Excuse me. I have a problem.
打搅一下. 我有个问题.
Yes sir. What's the problem?
是的 先生. 什么问题?
My laundry...
我洗好的衣服...
Oh no no,you don't come here.
Oh 不不, 你不用来这里.
We deliver it to your room.
我们送到你的房间去.
They did.
他们送来了.
They were just in my room.
他们刚刚在我的房间里.
But this isn't mine.
但是这不是我的.
Hm.What your room number?
Hm. 你的房间号是?
1711.
This is your room.
这是你的房间.
What's your name?
你的名字是?
Davis.
Jeff Davis.
This is your name.
这是你的名字
Do you have a red shirt?
你有一个红色的衬衫吗?
Yes,but this one doesn't belong to me.
是的, 但是这件不是我的.
What about blue pants?
蓝色的裤子呢?
Yes,they look like mine but they're not.
是的, 他们看起来像我的 但是不是我的.
Mr.Davis. Your room number,your name.
Mr. Davis, 你的房间号, 你的名字.
They look like your clothes.
他们看起来像你的衣服.
It must be your laundry.
那肯定是你的洗好的衣服.
Oh boy.
If this is mine,We have a small problem.
如果这是我的, 那么我们就有个小问题了
Small clothes,big problem.
小衣服, 大问题.